Guide to the Douglas C. Engelbart Papers M0638
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 1. Accession 1986-030
  - Drawings and Equations, [1959]; 1986-030 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence and Memos concerning Project EU 2821, 1986-030 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    [1959-60]
  - Project 2821. Early Papers by Engelbart, [1959]; 1986-030 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Project 2821. Charges and Records., [1959-1961]; 1986-030 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Project 2821. Notes., 1986-030 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Project 2821. Notes, [1959]; 1986-030 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Memo: Subsequent Evolution of an Application for the Two-aperture Core., 1986-030 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Project 2821. Misc., 1986-030 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - First Draft concerning Scaling., 1986-030 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Request-Correspondence for Engelbart's Scaling Paper., [1960]; 1986-030 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Engelbart: Microelectronics, And The Art Of Similitude, [1959]; 1986-030 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Talk Notes., 1960; 1986-030 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Paper. Fairchild Semiconductor Corporation. Solid State Micrologic Elements., 1986-030 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Notes for Microelectronics, and the Art of Similitude., [1960]; 1986-030 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Engelbart: Misc. Scratch, 1986-030 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Expense Vouchers, [1958]; 1986-030 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Microelectronics, general [Articles by Javitz, Feynman and Engelbart], 1960; 1986-030 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Conference information: "Man and Civilization: Control of the Mind"., 1961 Jan; 1986-030 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Information and notes for the "Annual Meeting of the American Documentation Institute (ADI)", 1960 Oct; 1986-030 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Phone Call Notes; List of the meetings of the Institute of Radio Engineers (IRE), [1960]; 1986-030 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Visitors of the Stanford Research Institute; Notes., [1958-1959]; 1986-030 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Information material from the visit at the University of Michigan, [June 1960]; 1986-030 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Conference at the University of Texas: IRE 4.10 Solid State Circuits Subcommittee Technical Discussion on Solid State Computer Circuits., [April/May 1959]; 1986-030 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - General material., [1959-1960]; 1986-030 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - 1959 Solid-State Circuits Conference. IRE-AIEE- University of Pennsylvania., 1959 Feb; 1986-030 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Papers and related materials for the "1959 Solid-State Circuits Conference"., 1986-030 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Notes for the Solid-State Circuits Conference., 1986-030 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Program of the "1959 Western Joint Computer Conference"; Notebook., [March 1959]; 1986-030 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Conference Schedules and Programs, [1958-59]; 1986-030 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Program, Papers and Notes for the "West Coast Joint Technical Meeting of the AIEE and the IRE"., 1960 Jan; 1986-030 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Engelbart, Lecture Notes, 1959 Nov; 1986-030 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Lecture for teachers of Ventura County, 1960 Feb; 1986-030 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Maps., 1986-030 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Computer Seminar Notes., 1986-030 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Keister's Lectures; Notes., [May 1955]; 1986-030 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence with Telemeter Magnetics, Inc.; Notes, [1957-1958]; 1986-030 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Notes and Cost Estimate Summaries for "Traveler Check Machine", [1957]; 1986-030 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Computer literature; Notes and: Ted R. Broida: "A History of High Intensity Sources of Radiant Energy", [1952]; 1986-030 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Computer Seminar Notes, [1956]; 1986-030 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Le Corbeilier's lecture series; Notes., [1955]; 1986-030 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - "Information for Proceedings Authors", 1954; 1986-030 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Datatron; Notes., 1986-030 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Articles and Papers of Louis Fein., [1959-1960]; 1986-030 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Papers and Bibliographies concerning Magnetic Computer Systems., [1958-1960]; 1986-030 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Maps., 1986-030 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Papers of the "Aeronutronic Systems, Inc.", [1958]; 1986-030 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Travel notes., [1958]; 1986-030 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Material and Correspondence for the "Western Eletronic Show & Convention (Wescon), 1959 Aug; 1986-030 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Information material for BIAX., 1959 Aug; 1986-030 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (with Charles P. Bourne?) on "Magnetism" and "thin films", [1959]; 1986-030 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - SRI Journal Number One 1958 (2 Copies) and Reprints of Engelbart's Paper: Facets of The Technical Information Problem. Correspondence with the Publisher., 1986-030 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Various Papers: Engelbart: Modified MAD-SAD Driving Arrangement which provides Increased Storage per Magnetic Element (Caterpillar Drive) [Febr. 1959]; Engelbart: A new all magnetic logic system using simple cores. [Dec. 1958]; Petersen: Technical Report on Access Methods for Magnetic Core Memories. [Febr. 1960]; Crane: A High Speed Logic System Using Magnetic Elements and Connected Wire Only., 1986-030 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Society for social responsibility in science: SSRS Newsletter No.25, 26, 27 & 29, 1954; 1986-030 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - U.C. Eletronics Newsletter, vol.1-4 (complete); scattered issues of vol.5-6., 1958-1963; 1986-030 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Notes on four-day visit to IBM facilities in New York State (SRI), 1958 Feb 11-14; 1986-030 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Memoranda on facility development; Man-Computer research at SRI., [1965]; 1986-030 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Douglas C. Engelbart: SRI Correspondence., [January 1964 - February 1966]; 1986-030 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Douglas C. Engelbart: SRI Correspondence., [February 1966 - December 1966]; 1986-030 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Douglas C. Engelbart: "Possibilities for Teaching Machine Activity at SRI"., [5/18/1960]; 1986-030 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Douglas C. Engelbart: "A possible research activity toward a technique for teaching coordinate physical skills.", [9/23/1960]; 1986-030 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Douglas C. Engelbart: Rough-Form Think Piece regarding research possibilities at SRI in areas of Man-Machine Communication Means, and automated Psycho-Moter skill training., [3/31/961]; 1986-030 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Text Manipulation Symposium., [April 13, 1964]; 1986-030 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Douglas C. Engelbart: "A Partial Essay on Man-Machine Intelligent-Team Reserch.", [March 10, 1960]; 1986-030 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Douglas C. Engelbart: Introducing our Thinkpiece on Man-Machine Communication means and automatic physical-skill training., [3-22-1961]; 1986-030 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Memorandum on SRI - SDC Transmission Lines., [May 12, 1964]; 1986-030 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence on requests for copies of Douglas C. Engelbart's research papers., [1964 -1967]; 1986-030 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence on requests for copies of Douglas C. Engelbart's research papers., [1964 - 1968]; 1986-030 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence on requests for copies of Douglas C. Engelbart's research papers., [1963 - 1964]; 1986-030 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - User's Guide for Off-line Text Manipulation System. MAW., [3/27/1967]; 1986-030 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Andrews and Ruflifson (SRI): "Three Meta. A Meta Compiler System for the SDS 940 (Rough Draft).", [12/29/1967]; 1986-030 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Invitation to the 6th "Bootstrap Seminar"., [March 1991]; 1986-030 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - User Guide Notes for a Work Station., [1967-1968]; 1986-030 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - General Introduction to the Additive Assembler., [1967]; 1986-030 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda. SOG., [1967]; 1986-030 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Notes concerning the Off-Line-System., [1967]; 1986-030 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda. AHI., [1963-1964]; 1986-030 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Papers on Man-Machine Communication., [1959-1961]; 1986-030 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous; D. C. Engelbart., [1958-1962]; 1986-030 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Patents by D.C. Engelbart., [1959]; 1986-030 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Further information on Engelbart patents, dockets, applications, etc., [1959/1960]; 1986-030 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Further material on Engelbart patents., [1961-63]; 1986-030 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Memoranda on Magnetic Systems., [1960]; 1986-030 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Series 2. Accession 1998-094
  - Alphabetical Files, 1962-1991
    - Alpha Files A-Z 1962
      - Augmented Human Intellect, 1961-1962 (Box 44, Folder 54)
      - Augmented Human Intellect Summary Report, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - First Keyset Algorithms, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 3)
      - How to Communicate Ideas, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - Man Machine Experiments, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - NIK Proposal, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - Operation Problem Solving, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - OSR, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - Reference Thinking, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - 3M, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - Vista-Book, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 10)
      - G3-BC, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 11)
      - Displays, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 12)
      - Input System, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 13)
      - Keyset Training, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 14)
      - MAC-SRI, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 15)
      - McIntosh, 1962-1964 (Box 44, Folder 16)
      - Notecards, 1963 (Box 44, Folder 17)
      - Orthagonal Magnetic Systems, 1963 (Box 44, Folder 18)
      - OSR, 1963 (Box 44, Folder 19)
      - Speedkey Proposal, 1963 (Box 44, Folder 20)
      - Stove Tube Display, 1963 (Box 44, Folder 21)
      - Transcription Central, 1963 (Box 44, Folder 22)
      - Cheap Station, 1963-1964 (Box 44, Folder 23)
      - NP, 1963-1966 (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - Alpha Files A-Z 1963-1964
      - AHI, 1963-1967 (Box 44, Folder 25)
      - Computer Simulated by People, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 26)
      - Direct-Connect TTY Code, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 27)
      - McIntosh, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 28)
      - NASA Proposal, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 29)
      - IGOA NLS, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 30)
      - Nucleus System, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 31)
      - Orthagonal Magnetic Systems, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 32)
      - OSR, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 33)
      - Project Planning, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 34)
      - Tapewriter, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 35)
      - Text Manipulation Symposium, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 36)
    - Alpha Files A-Z 1965
      - BC NP, 1964-1965 (Box 43, Folder 10)
      - Z Code, 1964-1965 (Box 43, Folder 11)
      - Augmented, 1964-1965 (Box 43, Folder 12)
      - DES & Plan History, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 13)
      - Elec-Mech Signals, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 14)
      - FJCC, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 15)
      - General Planning, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 16)
      - Keyset Codes History, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 17)
      - NASA, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 18)
      - Notebook XScript, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 19)
      - NP, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 20)
      - Processes, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 21)
      - RADC, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 22)
      - Skin Heaters, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 23)
      - 3100 RT-MM, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 24)
      - Thinkpiece, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 25)
      - Working Methodology, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - Alpha Files A-Z 1966
      - Old NL Files/Plans, 1965-1966 (Box 43, Folder 27)
      - Basic, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 28)
      - BC, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 29)
      - Current NL Work, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 30)
      - File Listings, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 31)
      - FLTS, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 32)
      - IPTO, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 33)
      - Old Press, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 34)
      - TLH Design Notes, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 35)
    - Alpha Files A-Z 1967
      - FLTS, 1966-1967 (Box 43, Folder 36)
      - NLS, 1966-1967 (Box 43, Folder 37)
      - ANET, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 38)
      - BTST, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 39)
      - Evans/Ball, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 40)
      - Evans, Dave, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 41)
      - FLTS User Guide, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 42)
      - Limits, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 43)
      - Links, Jumps, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 44)
      - Management, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 45)
      - Sponsor Conference, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 46)
      - DCE Old Workbook, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 47)
      - Watson, MA, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 48)
      - Calendar, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 49)
      - ARL, 1968-1969 (Box 43, Folder 50)
      - TODAS, 1968-1969 (Box 43, Folder 51)
      - BC NP History, 1967-1968 (Box 43, Folder 52)
      - Grist, 1967-1970 (Box 43, Folder 53)
    - Alpha Files A-Z 1970
      - Ball, Geoff, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - Baseline, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - BC NP, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - Bootstrap, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 8)
      - Caldoc, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 9)
      - Catalog, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 10)
      - Chi Notes, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 11)
      - Cost Analysis, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 12)
      - Current NP, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 13)
      - Deferred Exec. Des., 1970 (Box 38, Folder 14)
      - DRB, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 15)
      - Drum Decision, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 16)
      - WKE, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 17)
      - Executable Text, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 18)
      - 4792, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 19)
      - Higher Level Processes, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 20)
      - History, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 21)
      - Inform System, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 22)
      - Interactive Biblio Search, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 23)
      - Journal Transfer, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 24)
      - Managing Modern Complexity, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 25)
      - Meeting Notes, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 26)
      - Microform Notes, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 27)
      - NAS, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 28)
      - NASA, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 29)
      - Networks, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 30)
      - New NP, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 31)
      - NIC, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 32)
      - NILD, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 33)
      - Nixon Report, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 34)
      - NLS, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 35)
      - Norton, JC, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 36)
      - Notes, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 37)
      - NP, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 38)
      - Text Manipulation Systems, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 39)
      - Output to Work, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - Plans & NP, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - Portrayal Snapshots, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - Product File, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - Pre-Journal Archive, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - Relevance Memo, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Research Intelligence System (RINS), 1970 (Box 39, Folder 7)
      - Slide Catalog, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 8)
      - Special Notes, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 9)
      - SYDIA, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 10)
      - Structural Communication Thesis, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 11)
      - Tenex, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 12)
      - Working Notes, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Alpha Files A-S 1971
      - Misc. Unfiled, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - ARC, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - ARPA, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Augment, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Baseline Recs, System Design Proposal, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Bootstrap Community, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Baseline Record System, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Campus Computing Management, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Catalog Management System, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Center for Applied Linguistics, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - Collaboration with Information Science Groups, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - Command Language Evolution, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - Committee A, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - Computers & Community Handbook, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 15)
      - Computer Science Library, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 16)
      - CSIRO, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 17)
      - DEX, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 18)
      - Diagrams, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 19)
      - EMC, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 20)
      - General Workshop Data, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 21)
      - Grist, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 22)
      - Group X, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 23)
      - Group Y, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 24)
      - HDOC, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 25)
      - Infosys Appendix, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 26)
      - Interaction, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 27)
      - IPT, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 28)
      - IPTO, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 29)
      - Journal Memoranda, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Judge, Tony, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Link Syntax, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - MEAS, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - NAS, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - National Microfilm Association, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - New Documentation, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - New Plan, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - NLS NP, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - NIC, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - Needs & Possibilities, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - ONR, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - Organization Notes, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - Page Format Data, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 14)
      - PARC, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - Plan, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 16)
      - Presentation Diagrams, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - Programming, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 18)
      - Purdue, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 19)
      - R&D, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 20)
      - RADC, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 21)
      - Raw Scratch, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 22)
      - RINS, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 23)
      - SEAS Plan, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 24)
      - Set Prop, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 25)
      - Speech Project, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 26)
      - SRI, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 27)
      - System Features, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Alpha Files T-Z 1971
      - TD/NP, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - TENEX/NLS User Notes, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - TNLS, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Tools For Change, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Transcripts, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Travel Notes, D.C., 1971 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Visitors, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - What We Can Learn from Japanese Management, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - Xerox, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - NSF/ARPA, 1971-1972 (Box 22, Folder 11)
      - Meeting/Speaking, 1971-1972 (Box 22, Folder 12)
      - Bootstrap Community Old Notes, 1971-1973 (Box 22, Folder 13)
      - Post-NCC, 1971-1973 (Box 22, Folder 14)
      - NSF Dropped the Ball, 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 15)
      - Bootstrap Community, Org. Notes, 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Alpha Files A-N 1972
      - Misc. Unfiled, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 17)
      - Accounting, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 18)
      - Anderson/Coover, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 19)
      - ANET Science Journal, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 20)
      - ARC, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 21)
      - ARPA, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 22)
      - Baseline, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 23)
      - Bootstrap Community, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 24)
      - CAI, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 25)
      - CeNCoReL, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 26)
      - Center Inquiries, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 27)
      - Chi Suggestions re: NLS, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 28)
      - Cirad, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 29)
      - Communities, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 30)
      - Coordinated Information Services, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 31)
      - Design Review, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 32)
      - Development Coordination, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 33)
      - DNLS, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 34)
      - DPCS, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 35)
      - FRAMAC, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 36)
      - General Business, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 37)
      - ICCC, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 38)
      - Intra-Team Policy, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 39)
      - Journal Printouts, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 40)
      - KWAC, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 41)
      - KW for Policy Study Center, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 42)
      - LINAC, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 43)
      - L10, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 44)
      - Management Report, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 45)
      - 1972 (Box 22, Folder 46)
      - Matzorkis, G., 1972 (Box 22, Folder 46)
      - Michalaski, CF, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 47)
      - Miller, Lance, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 48)
      - MPS, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 49)
      - NBS, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 50)
      - National Information Center, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 51)
      - NLS, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 52)
      - NP, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 53)
      - NSF, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 54)
    - Alpha Files O-Z 1972
      - ONR, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 14)
      - Operations Review, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 15)
      - Organization, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 16)
      - Other Business, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 17)
      - Parker, Ed, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 18)
      - Penniman, W. David, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 19)
      - PERC, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 20)
      - Plan & NP Staff, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 21)
      - PODAL, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 22)
      - Productivity, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 23)
      - Prog Pres Notes, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 24)
      - Prop to SRI, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 25)
      - QWERTY versus Dvorak, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 26)
      - SDIS, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 27)
      - SEAS, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 28)
      - SIA, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 29)
      - Stefferud, Einar, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 30)
      - System Analyst Role, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 31)
      - Teleconference Session, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 32)
      - Tennant, Wes, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 33)
      - Thematic Slide Frames, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 34)
      - Utility Acquisition, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 35)
      - Utility Client Architecture Plan, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 36)
      - Viedo Projector, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 37)
      - Washington Office, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 38)
      - Work Organization, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 39)
    - Alpha Files A-D 1973
      - Misc. Unfiled, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 40)
      - AKW, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 41)
      - Analysis Notes, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 42)
      - APT, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 43)
      - ARC, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 44)
      - ASIS69, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 45)
      - Augmented Knowledge Workshop, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 46)
      - Backlinks, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 47)
      - Ballistic Research Labs, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 48)
      - BC, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 49)
      - Calls on Deck, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 50)
      - Cataloging Computing, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 51)
      - CBI, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 52)
      - CCC, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 53)
      - Charts, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 54)
      - CIA, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 55)
      - Command Language, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 56)
      - Command Info, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 57)
      - Computer Conferencing, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 58)
      - Computer Corp., 1973 (Box 39, Folder 59)
      - Computer Decisions, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 60)
      - COMSAT, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 61)
      - Contact Notes, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 62)
      - Datamation, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 63)
      - Delta 5000, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 64)
      - Development Plan, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 65)
    - Alpha Files E-R 1973
      - Editing Time Measurements, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 15)
      - Encrypt, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 16)
      - European Trip Contacts, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 17)
      - Forecasting, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 18)
      - Hansen, Scattered Team Research, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 19)
      - Hitachi, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 20)
      - I Colony, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 21)
      - Identifications, Access, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 22)
      - IPTO Meeting, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 23)
      - ISELI Resource, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 24)
      - Journal Citation Dialog, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 25)
      - Keyset, Chord, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 26)
      - KW SYS, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 27)
      - Licklider, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 28)
      - Line Processor, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 29)
      - University of London, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 30)
      - London Linked Dialog, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 31)
      - Looking at the Design Review Process, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 32)
      - LRPS - PR, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 33)
      - McIntosh Administration, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 34)
      - Management Cleanup Log, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 35)
      - Marchant Calculator, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 36)
      - Minicomputer, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 37)
      - MUNI Fiscal Plan, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 38)
      - National - Rochester, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 39)
      - NCC Data, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 40)